









portfolio (link)



Qualities

- team player
- ♦ thorough

- user test & research

Languages



Industrial Design Engineer

As a designer and engineer, I have developed a focus on the relationships we create between humans and the designed environment - the new behaviours and experiences they enable. I have a special affinity with well-being, spatial planning, user experience and innovation. In addition, I have learned that it is not only important to dream, but also to realise. This results in a hardworking and flexible person who motivates those around him to achieve the same goals - to make things happen!

Education

MSc Integrated Product Design, TU Delft

May 29th 2024

- product(-service) design
- technical prototyping
- stakeholdermanagement

- concept design
- design for manufacturing
- culture research
- Thesis 9/10 Empowering Psychosocial Well-Being at the Workplace. (link)

BSc Industrial Design Engineering, TU Delft

2021

- design thinking
- human-centred design
- brand identity design

- mechanics
- strategic design
- functional prototyping
- Thesis 7/10 Adaptive Urban Design against the Urban Heat Island Effect.

Minor Architecture, TU Delft

2019

- spatial planning
- model building
- design for public spaces

- trend analysis
- form- and modelstudy

Extracurricular

Ambassadors of Amsterdam

ongoing

Bildung Academy, Amsterdam

Determining and tackling a social problem in Amsterdam with a pilot as the final goal.

- involvement
- stakeholdermanagement
- working in a diverse group

- leadership
- project planning

Summer School 2 months

Aalto University, Helsinki

Designing environments in balance with nature in an international and multidisciplinary group.

- design for the future and
- stakeholdermanagement
- design for public spaces

- sustainability
- spatial planning

Exchange 6 months

Chalmers University, Gothenburg

Living in another country and immersing yourself in another culture. The four electives I took are:

- designing and evaluating user experiences
- form & manufacturing
- introduction in data science ا کی

- manufacturing strategy

design for disabilities

Internship

6 months

DigiNova, Delft

Designing robot applications for healthcare institutions and demented elderly in nursing homes.

- UI and UX design
- programmeren
- human-system interaction user testing

Work experience

Royal Ahrend

10/2023 - 05/2024

Graduation project. Research into behaviour, work culture, and well-being of employees (burnout).

- independent research and
- projectmanagement stakeholdermanagement
- behavioural design interaction design

- testing MBO Riinland
- teaching assistant

09/2019 - 06/2019

Frankeland - host in an elderly home 08/2012 - 02/2023

Noteworthy accomplishments

Micro-break communication tool

Royal Ahrend, HTC Eindhoven

Behavioural and cultural change in the workplace: a fight against the rising number of burnout.

research by design

- leading brainstorms
- co-creation

Naturale and playful seating outdoors

Aalto University, Helsinki

Becoming one with nature: a focus on functionality, sustainability, and local residents and other users.

minimalism

biodegradable design

Adjustable school chair

Royal Ahrend, Sint-Oedenrode

Office chair for Dutch primary education: adaptable for all students from 5 to 12 years old.

workshop experience

functional prototyping

personalised design

Adaptive and green city square

The Green Village, Delft

Bachelor's thesis: green solution for the urban heat island effect in the municipality of Delft.

spatial planning

adaptive design

I have been selected for the Human Factors NL thesis award and can speak at the HF conference. I was also chosen to speak at the Vital Work event of the Workplace Vitality Hub on the High Tech Campus.

I was selected by my faculty to participate in an international and multidisciplinary project on the use of wood in balance with nature.

High difficulty. An ergonomically almost impossible task, but I look back on it with great pleasure. Ahrend wants to realise and market the chair in the future.

Of all thirty participating students, my solution was selected by the organisation to continue working on.











2024

2023

2022

2021





CityOasis





Nature's seat



Hard skills

3D modeling

Rhinoceros

Visual communication

Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop Adobe InDesign Adobe Premiere

Digital prototyping

Adobe Dreamweaver Android Studio Figma Axure Adobe XD Arduino & Raspberry

Physical prototyping

Rapid Prototyping Workshop experienced

Design methodology

Double diamond

Knowledge of...

Python Mathlab